Ending
You got it?
We got it.
Yay!
So today I came to Kamakura on a garage train!
I've been saying that for a long time.
Yes, I have.
I'd like to take a stroll along Komachi-dori
Yes, sir
Let's start our trip to Kamakura in a hurry!
Let's start!
I came to this Komachi Dori, or rather, to this part of Kamakura.
I'm sure.
Yes.
I think it was quite a while ago when I was looking at the specific map.
Yes, we came here to eat happy pancakes.
That's right.
But I don't know what happened then. I guess we didn't have much time.
Not really.
I had to leave right away.
That's right.
It's my first time.
I'll come back later.
Okay.
So, this is my third or fourth time?
Fourth time?
You've been here a lot.
That's great.
With the kimonos and everything.
Yeah.
That's great.
Is there anything you like about it?
There are a lot of places.
But you said you wanted to go to the Matsucha place, right?
Yeah, I did.
That's a nice way to spend your allowance.
That's right.
I'll have to think about it.
It's going to run out.
That's how I feel.
Today, yes, indeed.
I would like to send you a picture of the daily life of a craftsman.
I'm like this in everyday life.
Yes.
We tend to eat the same things and go to the same places.
We tend to be the same.
That's right.
I'm... I'm...
It makes me sad to go alone.
I invite her on LINE.
And Shupe is a Buddha, so...
Buddha.
He's a Buddha, so...
He immediately says whatever you want to do.
I often go out with him.
It's fun.
Yes, in Kamakura.
Oh, wait, there's a pigeon.
Let's run away for a minute.
I'm scared.
It's just another day in the life!
Scary, scary!
Kamakura is really scary!
I've been asking Risa out.
I told her I liked her.
But she said it's too far away.
I kept getting turned down.
But, I got an OK for this trip.
I'm so happy!
It was a rather long trip, but...
But you know...
I've never been here before.
I'm looking forward to it.
What should we do?
I don't know what to eat.
Wait a minute. It's cute.
I think I like it. Here.I think I like it. Here.
Here?
You should try this one.
This one's pretty good.
Isn't this one pretty?
I'm a bit of an errand boy.
Let's do this one, then.
Okay.
Dumpling shop.
Can I see your menu?
The menu.
Three, this way, please.
Wait, what do you want?
What do you want? The limited edition?
I think you want the limited edition.
Seasonal.
Strawberry bean paste?
Strawberry or red bean paste.
But strawberry? I guess so...
Strawberry paste?
Yes.
I think I'll have Kuromitsu Mitarashi.
Looks good.
Looks so good!
I'm a sucker for limited editions, so I bought some.
It's so cute! I'll have the kuromitsu mitarashi.
Yum! Looks so good!
I think this is the first time I've bought dumplings here.
It's the first time, isn't it? So cute!
Yay! This one's not a horse.
It's a horse. I'd like to try some.
Here you go. Aren't they cute?
It's so cute. It looks so cute.
It's a rice cake. - It's pretty bite-size.
One bite's all I need. Here we go.
Here you go.
The mochi is soft.
I'll have the mashimashi with molasses.
Looks delicious.
Yes, it is.
Not soft?
Not soft? Mochi.
Too sweet! Yum!
I love sweet!
Molasses is right!
Indeed! Isn't the molasses hard?
You should try it too!
Try it! Let me feel it!
Finished eating the dumplings!
They have fresh baby sardines.
You have to go into the store.
What is it?
Looks good right now!
Looks delicious.
Is it famous for baby sardines?
It's like Shirasu Shonan.
Looks delicious!
Want some shirasu tempura?
Let's eat shirasu tempura!
Okonomiyaki looks delicious!
I'll have plain.
Plain is all baby sardines.
I see.
Then I'd like to order!
Wow, this camera!
Yeah!
All right. All right.
Oh, no.
But it's kind of serious.
We're in this together.
We're doing it together.
It's like we're doing it together.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm turning my private life around.
Yeah.
Look at this.
Ta-da!
I think you can see.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Looks delicious!
Mentaiko mayo, right?
Yay! It's on the edge.
Left side?
Yes, sir.
Ta-da!
Oh, and there's some nice light.
Wow, it's warm.
It's warm, isn't it?
Warm.
It's so white!
I want to take a picture.
Yay!
I'd like to take a picture here.
Here we go!
Cheese!
Cheese! Cheese! Cheese!
Okay. - Okay.
Okay.
Let's eat. Ready?
Bon appétit!
Crunchy!
Fluffy inside!
Fluffy!
Amazing!
Delicious!
Crunchy and crispy around the edges!
But it may be a little bit of baby sardines, no problem!
I can see it!
Yes!
Delicious!
So much baby sardines!
Oh, man!
I'll keep eating!
Now I'm going to continue on my way!
Go!
Wow!
More and more people!
So many people here!
Oh! We have candy strawberries!
I want a candy strawberry!
Eat it now!
Thank you!
Yay!
It's so cute!
I'm so happy!
Cute strawberry candy!
Candy strawberries!
Aah! What kind of a thing is that?
What kind of a thing is that?
Let's eat what kind!
You said you wanted to eat this!
Yes!
Candy strawberries!
Bon appétit!
Strawberry!
Looks delicious!
Tasty? Juicy?
Yes!
They're amazing! Strawberry candy's good!
It's so cute!
This is the best strawberry candy I've tasted in a long time!
Oh! Really?
There are many strawberry candies in many places!
But not at all?
Yes! Oh my God! Strawberry!
Try it!
Yeah! Matchy-matchy!
Like the big Buddha manjuu next to it.
It's delicious and cute.
Also, it's good luck!
I want to have good luck! Happiness!
That's what I call it!
I want to do good luck!
I want to do it!
What! You're not lucky!
What! I think I really need some luck!
Hold on! What do you want?
But you know what?
Shoestring bacon is good for business.Shoestring bacon is good for business.
You said it's in custard?
Yes!
Popular! What? Aren't they both good?
No! They're both good!
What should I do?
What do you want me to do? I don't know! I don't know! I don't know!
I think we should just go with taste.
I want both business and popularity.
The one you want to eat!
Great!
Let's see which one is more popular!
Always! Risa, you always ask!
Which is more popular?
Thank you very much!
Did you hear that?
See you later!
I'm back!
I wanted both popularity and a job.
But I wanted popularity.
I chose this one!
I want to see the face of the Great Buddha!
The Great Buddha... This way!
Yes! Can you see it?
Look!
Choo-choo!
You're so cute!
Oh! Wait! I don't think I can do this!
Pigeons...
I can't do this! I really can't!
Okay! Okay!
Let's get back on track.
I'm going to eat for popularity!
Get yourself together!
Yes! Please!
It's filled with so much custard!
Wow!
Yes!
It's so cute!
Boo-ya?
Then please go ahead with this!
So while I was eating Daibutsu-sama, I bought some fried chicken!
I really love it! My favorite food is karaage.
And it's Ko-chan's Kamakura karaage, which has won the Golden Lord award three years in a row!
Let's eat!
I can split this one in half.
Surely it comes in a four-piece package.
It's a four-pack!
So delicious!
The best fried chicken I've had recently!
It's the best I've had.
Everyone should definitely try this!
It won the gold medal three years in a row!
Yes, yes, yes.
There's a lot of it.
Then let's eat it.
I'll have some too.
Matcha latte.
I've seen this on social media and it looks delicious.
I also heard that it's made of matcha ice.
I was told to mix it and drink it, so I'm going to mix it and drink it.
It's so thick! It's so thick!
The color is just amazing!
I want to drink it every day!
I want to drink it for the rest of my life!
Subscription
I might want to get a subscription.
There are so many places in Kamakura!
I bet a bowl of rice topped with baby sardines would be delicious.
I'd love to try it!
But is it a restaurant?
I'll have to go in.
It's like...
Delicious!
There's always next time.
That's right.
Oh, man.
These hard bangs...
It's good.
You're doing a great job with the bangs.
These bangs are the best.These bangs are the strongest.
Oh, man.
We're doing great.
Your bangs aren't amazing.
Okay, then.
Let's move on.
See you next time.
I really can't get a shot of this.
You didn't close your eyes?